Euler Giachini

eulergiachini@gmail.com

+55 (67) 99637-3241

linkedin.com/in/euler-giachini-959053b9

Summary

I'm a Software Engineer with over 5 years of experience. I'm focused on Web3 development using Solidity, ethers.js, and Corda. I've also worked with the backend using Java with Spring Boot, in the fronted I used React.js, and Angular. I have a Bachelor's degree in Software Engineering.

Experience

Blockchain Engineer

Freelance (Self employed)

Jun 2022 - Present (1 year 6 months)

- Development of smart contracts with solidity.
- Complete integrations and assisted other developers by providing documentation and ensuring the integrations were successful.
- Create NFT contracts and marketplaces.
- Stack: Solidity, Node.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, EVM, ethers.js.

Blockchain Engineer

QAT Global | Custom Software Development

Oct 2022 - Jul 2023 (10 months)

- Development of Rest APIs with spring boot to provide services that interact with the blockchain.
- Development of smart contracts with solidity.
- Complete integrations and assisted other developers by providing documentation and ensuring the integrations were successful.
- Stack: Java, SpringBoot, Gemini, Solidity, Node.js, JavaScript, EVM, ethers.js.

Blockchain Engineer

Holonic

Feb 2022 - May 2022 (4 months)

- Holonic creates high-functioning "POD" teams that positively the sustainability and the systems within Silicon Valley startups from the inside out.
- In Holonic as a Product Oriented Development team member, where we work collaboratively instead of individually. We are capable of delivering incremental value every week, in an autonomous agile team with critical thinking skills to contribute even with business decisions. My technical responsibility includes creating smart contracts following the best design and security patterns.
- Agile Methodology: Scrum
- Stack: Solidity, Node.js, EVM, Corda, Java, Kotlin.

Senior Systems Development Analyst

Extreme Digital Solutions - EDS

Sep 2021 - Feb 2022 (6 months)

- Carrying out bug fixes and implementation of new features in applications.
- Implementation of unit tests in applications.
- Stack: Spring, Jira, Azure, Git, GitLab, Java 8 / 11 (Springboot), PostgreSQL, Oracle, Dbeaver, Restful API, Docker.



🜆 Systems Development Analyst

Extreme Digital Solutions - EDS

Jun 2021 - Feb 2022 (9 months)

- Carrying out bug fixes and implementation of new features in applications.
- Implementation of unit tests in applications.
- Stack: Spring, Jira, Azure, Git, GitLab, Java 8 / 11 (Springboot), PostgreSQL, Oracle, Dbeaver, Restful API, Docker.

Software Developer

Perfor Máguinas

Feb 2021 - May 2021 (4 months)

- Acting in Java language development.
- Carry out national and international trips on customer visits, installing and providing software training.
- Assist in the development of high-performance systems.
- Plan and execute software tests. Support the customer.

Software Developer

Freelancer

Jun 2019 - Feb 2021 (1 year 9 months)

- -Full-Stack Developer (Java) for Electronic Tax Documents (NF-e, NFC-e).
- -Developed asset traceability for a company that tracks coffee.
- -Stack: Java SE, AngularJS, React.js, Spring, Corda, Java Swing, JMS, JavaFX, Hibernate, PostgreSQL.

Intern

EasyPostal

Aug 2017 - Jun 2019 (1 year 11 months)

-Full-Stack Developer (PHP, C# / Angular).

-MySQL database.

∧ Intern

LupaAzul

Aug 2016 - Jul 2017 (1 year)

- Develop test cases for each requirement created in the system.
- Run functional tests.
- Report and document bugs.

Education

UDESC - Ceavi

Bacharel, Software Engineering 2015 - 2019

Skills

TypeScript • ethers.js • EVM (Ethereum Virtual Machine) • Hardhat • Truffle Framework • Java • PostgreSQL • Spring Framework